Dima Snisarenko Frontend Developer

Last update: Tue Jan 09 2018 11:07:56 GMT+0100 (CET)

The online version is available at https://sneas.github.io/cv

Biography

Residence

Weesp, Dichtershof, NL

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitry-snisarenko-74a4b830/

Email

snisarenkodima@gmail.com

Languages

English, Russian, Dutch on a primitive level

Excited about computer programming, automation, typography and graphics since 1996.

Visual and animation designer for the local TV channel between 2000 and 2003.

Started professional career as a fullstack LAMP developer in 2005.

Remote freelancer between 2010 and 2014. Some feedbacks are available here (https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/_~01752134695731685e/).

Pure frontender since 2012.

Employment

KLM Royal Dutch Airlines

Senior frontend developer

Feb 2017 - present

Project: Real time mobile application used by KLM mechanics in Schiphol airport.

 $ig(\mathsf{Angular} \ \mathsf{5} ig) ig(\mathsf{Ionic} \ \mathsf{3} ig) ig(\mathsf{Redux} ig) ig(\mathsf{RxJS} ig) ig(\mathsf{Typescript} ig) ig(\mathsf{SASS} ig) ig(\mathsf{Webpack} \ \mathsf{2} ig) ig(\mathsf{Karma} ig)$

Knab hypotheken

Senior frontend developer

Jun 2014 - Feb 2017

Project: Registration flow, mortgage tools

Responsibilities: Maintain existing project and provide new tools and components.

Main achievements: Backbone -> Angular 1.3 transition. Introduction of TDD with Karma and E2E with Protractor. Angular 1.3 -> Angular 1.5 transition.

```
AngularJS Karma Protractor SASS Gulp Bootstrap Heroku
```

upwork.com

Senior frontend developer

Oct 2012 - Jun 2014

A high traffic website. The biggest player on freelance job market.

Responsibilities: Maintain existing application, developed new features and components.

Main achievements: Introduction of TDD process with PHPUnit and qUnit. Job post template engine.

```
(Javascript)(jQuery)(qUnit)(GruntJS)(Selenium)(Compass/SASS)(PHP)
```

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. Sevastopol State Technical University [2002 – 2007]

Certification

- Zend Certified Engineer PHP 5.3 Jan 24, 2011
- React Nanodegree Dec 27, 2017
 Projects accomplished:
 - https://github.com/sneas/myreads React
 - https://github.com/sneas/readable React Redux
 - https://github.com/sneas/mobile-flashcards React Native Redux

Additional experience

A complete list of side/hobby projects: https://github.com/sneas.

Some cool projects:

Component Library

https://github.com/sneas/component-library

The easiest way to create HTML component library for existing website.



A solution to CORS problem of Ionic and WKWebView

https://github.com/sneas/ionic-native-http-connection-backend

This project's become quite popular since Ionic made WKWebView a default web container.

Namespaced Bootstrap

https://github.com/sneas/bootstrap-sass-namespace

Non-conflicting bootstrap integration. Consider using this project if Bootstrap has to be applied partially. ie to particular div of a page.

Bootstrap SASS